<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="hub.top.com.microsoft.schemas.visio"
      label="Visio XML import"
      version="1.0.0"
      provider-name="service-technology.org">

   <description>
      Visio XML importer.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Visio 2003 XML Schema Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation. All
rights reserved. Eclipse packages and parsers for reading Microsoft
Visio 2003 XML files Copyright (c) Dirk Fahland 2008, 2010.

This package is part of the Service-Technology.org Modeling Languages.

This program and the accompanying materials are made available under
the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0, or alternatively the
GNU Affero General Public License Version 3 (or later), see LICENSE file. 
   
Copyright (c) 2008, 2010 Dirk Fahland.

Dirk Fahland, Institut fuer Informatik,
Lehrstuhl Theorie der Programmierung, Humboldt-Universitaet zu Berlin.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      The right to implement Visio 2003 XML Schema has been granted
by the Microsoft Open Specification Promise. http://www.microsoft.com/interop/osp/.

This package and the accompanying materials are made available under
the terms of

 - the Eclipse Public License v1.0 (&quot;EPL&quot;), which accompanies this
   distribution, and is available at
   http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html,

OR ALTERNATIVELY

 - the GNU Affero General Public License Version 3 or later (&quot;AGPL&quot;), which
   accompanies this distribution, and is available at
   http://www.gnu.org/licenses/agpl-3.0-standalone.html,
   
Software distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; basis,
WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License
for the specific language governing rights and limitations under the
License.

For Original Creators and Contributors, and the respective copyright
ownership, see AUTHORS file. 

If you wish to allow use of your version of this file only under the terms
of the AGPL and not to allow others to use your version of this file under
the terms of the EPL, indicate your decision by deleting the provisions
above and replace them with the notice and other provisions required by the 
AGPL. If you do not delete the provisions above, a recipient may use your
version of this file under the terms of any one of the EPL or the AGPL.

The following material is made available only under the terms of the EPL.
  - all files in ./icons/full/ and its subdirectories
  
If you wish to redistributed this package or works that base on this
package under terms which are not compatible with the EPL, please remove
all aforementioned material that is only made available the terms of the
EPL.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Seda Updates" url="http://download.gna.org/service-tech/seda/updatesite/"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.xmi"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.edit"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.edit.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="hub.top.com.microsoft.schemas.visio._2003.vdx"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="hub.top.com.microsoft.schemas.visio._2003.vdx.edit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="hub.top.com.microsoft.schemas.visio._2003.vdx.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
